http://www.northsteltoname.org/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY
1. Our Commitment to Privacy. This notice describes our Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy is designed to advise you about how we collect, use, and protect the Personally Identifiable Information you provide. By visiting this site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.2. What Information is Collected.(a) Information You Provide to Us:We collect the Personally Identifiable Information you choose to enter on various pages of our site, or that you may choose to give us in some other way (such as by email, physical mail, or by telephone). For example, you will be asked to provide Personally Identifiable Information when you access or register for access to certain portions of our site or sign up for newsletters or mailings.The categories of Personally Identifiable Information we collect are your first and last name, e-mail address and telephone number, but you may choose to include more personally identifiable information when you use certain services on our site.You can choose not to provide certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of our services and features.(a) Automatic Information:When you visit a website, you disclose certain information, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the time of your visit. This site, like many other sites, records this basic information about visits to our site.(b) Cookies:Cookies are pieces of information that are transferred to your computer from a web server.We use cookies to store visitor preferences, record session information, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site and to customise Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or you can change your settings to refuse to accept cookies.3. How and When the Information is Used. The information we collect is used for administering our business activities as follows:(a) Provided to the recruitment agencies you contact with feedback of who made contact with them. We do not use this information for marketing purposes or to add you to unsolicited mailing lists.4. How We Protect Your Information.The privacy and protection of your information is important to us. We offer some of our services in connection with our other web sites that we own.5. Who Has Access to the Information.Information about our users is important to us. Access to your information is never provided to third parties. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order and we may disclose your information when we believe we are required to do so by law. We may disclose your information in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us and to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure.6. MethodsWe Use to Protect Your Information.We follow Data Protection Guidelines to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. In addition, our business practices are reviewed periodically for compliance with policies and procedures governing the security and confidentiality of our information. Our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorised persons.7. How You Can Access Your Information.You can request access to all your personally identifiable information maintained by us by sending an e-mail to us at the address listed below. Upon request we offer you the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in your personally identifiable information. You can have this information corrected by sending us an e-mail at the address listed below.8. Consent.By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.9. Changes to Privacy Policy.If our Privacy Policy or procedures change, we will immediately post those changes to our website. Any such changes will be effective immediately upon being posted, unless otherwise stated in the change.10. Effective Date.This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 25th, 2016.11. Contact E-Mail.You may contact us concerning this Privacy Policy by using any of the contact options shown on this site.
privacy@demolink.org
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website.
